Viktor Bajs-Jovanović

Birth date 26.02.1994 in Osijek, Croatia

Marital status Single

Nationality Croatian



Academic Career

2000 - 2002 Primary school Čepin "Osnovna škola Vladimira

Nazora Čepinski Martinci"

2002 - 2008 Primary school Šećerana "Osnovna škola Šećerana,

Branjin Vrh"

2008 - 2012 High school Beli Manastir "Prva srednja škola Beli

Manastir" - Degree: Education entrance qualification

(Matura)

2012 - 2015 Josip Juraj Strossmayer University in Osijek (at

Electrical Engineering Faculty)

Degree: Bachelor

Electrial engineer - Direction: Computer Science

Thesis: Functions in programming language "C"

Professional background

04/2014 - 06/2014 School internship in the High School Beli

Manastir as scientific and educational assistant

(Assistant Professor)

03/2014 - 08/2014 <u>T-HT (Croatian Telekom)</u>

Osijek, Croatia

o Call Center Agent in Technical Support

Viktor Bajs-Jovanović

10/2014 - 01/2015 <u>EcoCortec d.o.o. (GmbH)</u>

Beli Manastir, Croatia

Computer scientist

01/2016 - 03/2016 Tehno Filter d.o.o. (GmbH)

Beli Manastir, Croatia

o Own warehouse management program

"INVICTUS"

04/2016 - 05/2016 ABBA Bank und Leasing Software

Bilje, Croatia

Junior Software Developer

06/2017 - 06/2018 Geisberger Gesellschaft BioGas

Schwindegg, Germany

o Electrician

06/2018 - 07/2018 Netzwerkservice Fischer

Buchbach, Germany

o IT-System Electrician

09/2018 - **Employed**

Altötting, Germany

PC-Programmer (Software Developer,
Maintenance/Implementation/Evaluation/Furthe
r development of the program, Customer Care...)

Viktor Bajs-Jovanović

Languages

- o Croatian Native
- o English B1 Level
- o German B1 Level

Software

- o C#
- o WPF Blazor WinForms MYSQL MS Office
- o C++ SQL SQLite MongoDB HTML CSS
- o Xamarin Docker Bootstrap
- o Javascript React Native

Interests

Hobbies Chess, Football, Swiming, Fitness

Other Driving license class B